

# Yashraj Bhardwaj

Delhi, India+91-9971173173

2016 - 2017

www.yashrajbhardwaj.in

# Co-Founder - Zenith Vipers Group , Workolab & Partner - Ensure Equity LLP

#### **SUMMARY**

Yashraj is 20 years old and Co-Founder of Zenith Vipers Group (group of companies based in India, United Arab Emirates and Hong Kong. He own 36 Research Projects and 15 patent applications that he has filed in a team. He is also the recipients of Karmaveer Chakra Award 2016 and have also been named amongst top 10 young entrepreneurs of 2016 across the globe by by success magazine. He is finalist of SF fellowship worth \$250000 and winners of \$100000. He is also proud nominee of Padma Shri 2018, one of the highest civilian award in India. Also winner of many international and national awards. Yashraj resides in Delhi and is very closely connected with the latest in technology and innovation around the world, with very close association with innovation powerhouses like Silicon Valley giants, TED, Venture Firms and Technology Clusters around the world. He is forbes 30 Under 30 asia 2018

## Work experience

### **Managing Director**

**IDEAX Solutions LLC** 

#### Co-Founder

Co-Founder

Incuspaze

Prometheus Solutions SPV

| CEO, Co-Founder<br>Zenith Vipers        | 2015 - Present |
|-----------------------------------------|----------------|
| Co-Founder & Partner Ensure Equity      | 2018 - Present |
| Co-Founder<br>Workolab                  | 2017 - Present |
| Investor, Advisor Space India           | 2017 - Present |
| Investor, Technical Advisor Instaprintz | 2017 - Present |

#### Education

**High School** 2014 - 2015

Indraprastha World School

Senior Secondary 2016 - 2017

Indraprastha World School

Subjects-Sciences

## **Major Highlights**

Forbes
Awarded Forbes 30 under 30

Eagle Award

Government of Malaysia

Padma Shri

Nominated for year 2018 &. 2019

Novus Summit

Youngest Invited Delegation at United Nations, New York

KARMAVEER CHAKRA

In association with United Nations for work in Research and Development

SF FELLOW

For Research and Development worth USD 125,000

AUSTRIAN GRANT

For one of the major patent worth USD 45,000

Named as Top 10 Young Entrepreneur across the globe, March, 2017 feature.

MeltingPot 2020
Innovator of the Year

Global Startup Award,

Global Startup Award,

Geneva

Geneva

Nordic Grant Prize Grant

of 430,000 NOK (50,000 USD)



# Other Highlights

- Presented research papers at many conferences, IIT's and other premier institutes.
- Qualified to represent India at various international fairs and Conferences
- Scholar at World Health Innovation Summit.
- Part of the youngest invited delegation for Novus Summit by United Nations
- Recognised as Category A research Scholars by National Science Center, Delhi.
- Speakers at Indian Youth Conclave and Under25 club, India.

Created with 🔽 VisualCV